<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio website for Ozlem Cuhaci</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio website for Ozlem Cuhaci</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brexit</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog7/</guid>
      <description>Image Source: Britannica © vchalup/Fotolia [Accessed 19 Sept. 2020]
How political affiliation translated to Brexit voting General Election 2015 and Brexit 2016 As you all know Brexit is the withdrawal of the United Kingdom from the European Union. Following a UK-wide referendum in June 2016, 52% of British citizens voted in favour of leaving the EU and 48% voted to remain a member. One year ago in 2015, there was another election, general election of UK where Conservative, Labour, Liberal Democrats and UK Independence Party were the canditates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMdB Analysis</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog5/</guid>
      <description>Image Source: Amazon.jobs [Accessed 19 Sept. 2020]
What affects a movie’s box office success? Analysis of movies in the IMDB dataset IMDb (also known as the Internet Movie Database) is an online database, owned by Amazon, of information related to films, television programs, home videos, video games, and streaming content online – including cast, production crew and personal biographies, plot summaries, trivia, ratings, and fan and critical reviews. IMDb has approximately 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TfL Bike Rentals</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog6/</guid>
      <description>Image Source: Intelligenttransport [Accessed 19 Sept. 2020]
How does the number of bike rentals change through the years? Excess rentals in TfL bike sharing I’ll analyze Transport for London bike sharing data to inspect how do the number of bike rentals change between 2015 and 2020. I’ll visualize monthly and weekly changes in the number of rentals through the years.
I get the data from London Datastore
url &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;https://data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>